welivesecurity.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy policy | WeLiveSecurity

ESET, spol. s r.o., having its registered office at Einsteinova 24, 851 01 Bratislava, Slovak Republic, registered in the Commercial Register administered by Bratislava I District Court, Section Sro, Entry No 3586/B, Business Identification Number: 31 333 535 (hereinafter referred to as “We”, “Us”, “ESET”) respects the privacy of our users and takes great care to protect your personal data. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of this Site (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”). When leaving this Site, please read the Privacy Policy applicable to the Site you are thereafter visiting. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. By entering and using this Site you (hereinafter referred to as “You”) declare your agreement with this privacy statement, You expressly accept and give your unambiguous consent that Your Personal Information gained with registration on this Site, or in connection with your use of the Site, with respect to the Site, may be transferred across international borders to server locations supporting the Site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your registration) for operating and developing the Site, including transfers to ESET subcontractors, agents or representatives, who perform tasks related to the Site and services, or for the purposes of storing the data in relevant databases.

**Links**

This Site may contain links to third party websites. Please note that we do not take responsibility for the privacy policy of such websites; therefore whenever you to other websites, make sure to read their privacy policy statements.

**Non-personal information automatically collected**

ESET is committed to protecting the privacy of Site visitors. This Site gathers certain information such as internet protocol (IP), internet service provider (ISP), operating system, demographic information, and browser type, on a statistical basis only. This information is not linked to any specific personal entity. Please note that ESET may provide aggregate statistics about its users, traffic patterns and other statistics of certain activities related to Site, to trusted third parties in order to continue improving this Site, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information.

**Personal information**

ESET collects Personal Information You provide Us for the purposes of provision, development and personalization of the Site, technical administration, services and/or products, research and demographics, statistics, user support including our personal communication with You in order to respond to Your requests. Such information may include, among other information, Your name, nickname, e-mail address, password and location information. If you send any material to the Site, we might have to contact You in order to gain additional information necessary for processing or fulfillment of Your requirements and purposes for use of this Site.

Registration, if required is performed via your social network account. ESET may access your name, gender, link to your profile, profile picture, location. You can control permissions in your social network account in compliance with Privacy Policy of particular social network.

**Personal information security**

Please note that while there are always risks associated with providing Personal Information, whether in person, by phone or over the Internet or any other media, and no system of technology is completely safe, “tamper” or “hacker-proof”, ESET has endeavoured to take appropriate measures to prevent and minimize risks of unauthorized access to, improper use and the inaccuracy of Your Personal Information. For example when collecting or transferring sensitive data  we use encrypting technology. We make sure that personal information provided by You will be kept accurate and secured in accordance with industry standards and technology.

**Accuracy of collected data**

ESET will on its own initiative, or at Your request, replenish, rectify or erase any in-complete, inaccurate or outdated personal information retained by ESET in connection with the operation of this Site.

**Your rights**

You have the right to access, modify, correct and eliminate information You provided to Us, including rights of data subject according Act on Personal Data Protection. We will comply with Your requests unless there is a legal obligation which prevents us from such action .

**Data retention**

Your personal information will be retained until You close Your account or We close it when You fail to follow Terms of Service of this Site. We will continue retaining information about You in the minimum volume in order to meet legal requirements and to enforce this Privacy Policy. However, we may retain data that are not of personally identifiable nature.

**Visitors’ identification / cookies**

Generally, You may use this Site for information purposes without giving personal information and informing ESET who You are. But, from time to time, ESET or its third-party designees may place information on Your computer to allow ESET to collect certain data. This information is commonly known as a “cookie”. Cookies are small text files and are commonly used on many websites to provide users with a more efficient experience. Cookies are stored on Your hard disc in the computer, not on the Site. Cookies allow us to serve You better and more efficiently, and to personalize Your experience at our site. Through the use of cookies, ESET is able to further maintain, develop and improve the Site. No personal information about You is gathered through the use of these types of cookies. In other words, cookies are identifying Your computer, not You. If You do not wish to receive cookies, or You want to be notified when a cookie is set, You can configure Your browser to do this, if Your browser offers this functionality. If You choose to decline some cookies, be aware that You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site, nor will You be able to download certain content and/or take part in certain activities on the Site. It is possible to block all cookies but this may result in diminished functionality or non-functionality of the Site. Cookies enable us to recognize Your computer when you revisit our Site. We do not use cookies to collect personal information about you. This Site may also facilitate third party cookies such as those from Google Analytics, etc. We do not hold responsibility for third party cookies or how they collect information about Your visit on this Site. Therefore, make sure to read their privacy policies. Available Cookie Opt-out – Google Analytics: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

**Information disclosure**

Without Your prior consent, We do not and will not disclose information we gathered about You to any third party other than parties affiliated with Us (any legal entity within ESET Group). However, we are entitled to provide personally identifiable information about You to our subcontractors and other partners on a “need to know basis” (when disclosure is reasonable necessary) and only in connection with the need to maintain or improve certain functions and activities of this Site. We make sure that such third parties are properly advised and instructed on how to deal with your personal information and how to protect it. However, we don’t need Your consent the event that we are required to provide information we collected about You by legal authorities if such obligation is given by law or court.

**Minors**

No information may be submitted to ESET via the Site by persons who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event You are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from Your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to ESET via this Site, with the exception that such activities are allowed by applicable law of Your country.

**Limitation of liability**

To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, in no event shall the provider, its employees or licensors be liable for any lost profits, revenue, sales, data or costs of procurement of substitute goods or services, property damage, personal injury, interruption of business, loss of business information or for any special, direct, indirect, incidental, economic, cover, punitive, special or consequential damages, however caused and whether arising under contract, tort, negligence or other theory of liability, arising out of the use of or inability to use this site, even if the provider or its affiliates are advised of the possibility of such damages. Because some countries and jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of liability, but may allow liability to be limited, in such cases, the liability of the provider, its employees or licensors or affiliates shall be limited to the sum of 100 €.

**Severability**

Should any of the provisions hereof be or become unenforceable, inapplicable, invalid or illegal, this shall not affect the validity of the other provisions hereof, which shall remain valid and enforceable in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Should any of the provisions hereof be or become unenforceable, inapplicable, invalid or illegal, such invalidity being caused by any of its parts, such provision shall continue to be valid as if the invalidating part was omitted.

**Contact**

Any notices, requests, comments regarding this Privacy Policy, shall be mailed to website provider: ESET, spol. s r.o., Einsteinova 24, 851 01 Bratislava, Slovak Republic. Data processor according Personal Data Protection Law is Mediablaze Group Ltd, of Chester House, Kennington Park Business Centre, 1-3 Brixton Road, London, SW9 6DE.

**Modification of privacy policy**

ESET reserves the right to change or modify at any time this Privacy Policy, or change, modify or deny access to this Site, or its content without prior notice.
